Dennis DeConcini Papers 1944-2008
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 3: Congressional Activities. 1944-1998
  - Series 9: Issue Files, 1967-1994
    - Subseries 1: Arizona Issues. 1967-1994
      - Health and Human Services-Federal Food Assistance Programs. 1992 (Box 421, Folder 5)
      - Health and Human Services-Foundation for Senior Living. 1983-1985 (Box 421, Folder 6)
      - Health and Human Services-Garden Park Enterprises. 1983-1988 (Box 421, Folder 7)
      - Health and Human Services-Gila Bend Drug Treatment Center. 1990-1991 (Box 421, Folder 8)
      - Health and Human Services-Girlstown. 1978 (Box 421, Folder 9)
      - Health and Human Services-Grants. 1988-1992 (Box 421, Folder 10)
      - Health and Human Services-Health Care Costs. 1982-1994 (Box 421, Folder 11-12)
      - Health and Human Services-Health Care to the Homeless. 1988 (Box 421, Folder 13)
      - Health and Human Services-Health Systems. 1977-1992 (Box 421, Folder 14)
      - Health and Human Services-High School Drug Use. 1988-1990 (Box 421, Folder 15)
      - Health and Human Services-Hunger Programs. 1985-1986 (Box 421, Folder 16)
      - Health and Human Services-Legal Services. 1990 (Box 421, Folder 17)
      - Health and Human Services-Legislation. 1987 (Box 421, Folder 18)
      - Health and Human Services-Maryvale Cancer Center. 1987-1992 (Box 421, Folder 19-21)
      - Health and Human Services-Mental Illness. 1990-1991 (Box 421, Folder 22)
      - Health and Human Services-National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism Proposal. no date (Box 422, Folder 1)
      - Health and Human Services-National Network of Learning Disabled Adults. 1985 (Box 422, Folder 2)
      - Health and Human Services-Nogales Cancer Cluster. 1993-1994 (Box 422, Folder 3)
      - Health and Human Services-Nursing Homes. 1984-1993 (Box 422, Folder 4)
      - Health and Human Services-Physicians Health Plan. 1986 (Box 422, Folder 5)
      - Health and Human Services-Runaway and Homeless Youth. 1991 (Box 422, Folder 6)
      - Health and Human Services-Seniors Security Forum. 1981-1991 (Box 422, Folder 7)
      - Health and Human Services-Social Security Disability Issues. 1989-1990 (Box 422, Folder 8)
      - Health and Human Services-State Aging Administration. 1985-1986 (Box 422, Folder 9)
      - Health and Human Services-Substance Abuse in Arizona Survey. 1990 (Box 422, Folder 10)
      - Health and Human Services-Substance Abuse Prevention. 1992 (Box 422, Folder 11)
      - Health and Human Services-Tucsonans for a Drug-Free Workplace. 1991-1993 (Box 422, Folder 12)
      - Health and Human Services-Vision Quest. 1977-1985 (Box 422, Folder 13)
      - Health and Human Services-Vocational Rehabilitation. 1984-1985 (Box 422, Folder 14)
      - Health and Human Services-Youth Programs. 1986-1994 (Box 422, Folder 15)
      - Housing-Development. 1977-1994 (Box 422, Folder 16-17)
      - Housing-Federal Disaster Assistance. 1975-1986 (Box 422, Folder 18)
      - Housing-Homeless. 1988-1990 (Box 422, Folder 19)
      - Housing-Housing and Urban Development. 1977-1994 (Box 422, Folder 20)
      - Housing-Schlomowitz, Fanny; Holocaust Restitution Payments. 1993-1994 (Box 422, Folder 21)
      - Housing-Tucson House. 1977-1992 (Box 423, Folder 1)
      - Housing-Westward Ho Project. 1977-1980 (Box 423, Folder 2)
      - Labor. 1984-1988 (Box 423, Folder 3)
      - Law Enforcement-Criminal Justice Grants. 1990-1991 (Box 423, Folder 4)
      - Law Enforcement-Criminal Justice Surveys. 1979-1992 (Box 423, Folder 5)
      - Law Enforcement-Drug Enforcement. 1992-1993 (Box 423, Folder 6)
      - Law Enforcement-Illegal Wiretapping Investigation. 1977 (Box 423, Folder 7)
      - Law Enforcement-Police Hiring. 1993-1994 (Box 423, Folder 8)
      - Law Enforcement-Prisons. 1987-1994 (Box 423, Folder 9)
      - Mining-Arizona Smelters. 1977-1980 (Box 423, Folder 10)
      - Mining-Copper Industry. 1977-1994 (Box 423, Folder 11-12)
      - Mining-Lalor, Vince. 1985-1992 (Box 423, Folder 13)
      - Mining-Mines. 1987-1992 (Box 423, Folder 14)
      - Parks and Recreation-Catalina State Park. 1987-1988 (Box 423, Folder 15)
      - Parks and Recreation-Grand Canyon National Park. 1976-1994 (Box 423, Folder 16-17)
      - Parks and Recreation-Historic Preservation. 1989-1993 (Box 423, Folder 18)
      - Parks and Recreation-Land and Water Conservation Fund. 1987-1988 (Box 423, Folder 19)
      - Parks and Recreation-National Park Service. 1983-1992 (Box 424, Folder 1)
      - Parks and Recreation-Petrified Forest National Park. 1992 (Box 424, Folder 2)
      - Parks and Recreation-Rio Salado Project Financing. 1984-1987 (Box 424, Folder 3)
      - Parks and Recreation-Saguaro National Monument. 1986-1994 (Box 424, Folder 4-5)
      - Parks and Recreation-Saguaro National Monument Expansion Act. 1993 (Box 424, Folder 6)
      - Parks and Recreation-Saguaro National Monument Land Exchange. 1986-1987 (Box 424, Folder 7)
      - Parks and Recreation-Saguaro National Monument Old Yuma Mine. 1983-1993 (Box 424, Folder 8)
      - Parks and Recreation-Saguaro National Monument Road. 1982-1988 (Box 424, Folder 9)
      - Parks and Recreation-Walnut Canyon National Monument. 1994 (Box 424, Folder 10)
      - Parks and Recreation-Winslow Tree Stump Project. 1975-1978 (Box 424, Folder 11)
      - Politics. 1976-1994 (Box 424, Folder 12-13)
      - Politics-Correspondence. 1976-1987 (Box 424, Folder 14-16)
      - Politics-Napolitano, Janet. 1992-1994 (Box 424, Folder 17)
      - Resources-Central Arizona Project. 1967-1993 (Box 424, Folder 18)
      - Resources-Central Arizona Project. 1967-1993 (Box 425, Folder 1)
      - Resources-Gasoline. 1979-1986 (Box 425, Folder 2)
      - Resources-Waste Resources Committee. 1980-1984 (Box 425, Folder 3-4)
      - Resources-Water. 1976-1994 (Box 425, Folder 5)
      - Science and Technology-Biosphere II. 1982 (Box 425, Folder 6)
      - Science and Technology-Goldwater Science Center. 1983-1988 (Box 425, Folder 7)
      - Science and Technology-International Science and Engineering Fair. 1985 (Box 425, Folder 8)
      - Science and Technology-Kitt Peak Observatory. 1989-1990 (Box 425, Folder 9)
      - Science and Technology-Mt. Graham Observatory. 1988-1994 (Box 425, Folder 10)
      - Science and Technology-Steward Observatory/Max Plank Telescope Project. 1979-1985 (Box 425, Folder 11)
      - Telecommunications-Cable Deregulation. 1990 (Box 425, Folder 12)
      - Telecommunications-Cable Vision. 1978-1979 (Box 425, Folder 13)
      - Telecommunications-Nogales Non-Directional Radio Beacon. 1984 (Box 425, Folder 14)
      - Telecommunications-Radio. 1978-1990 (Box 425, Folder 15)
      - Telecommunications-Telephone. 1982-1988 (Box 425, Folder 16)
      - Telecommunications-Television. 1977-1994 (Box 425, Folder 17)
      - Telecommunications-U.S. Forest Service Telecommunication Site Fees. 1990-1993 (Box 425, Folder 18)
      - Transportation-Airlines, Cochise. 1976-1981 (Box 425, Folder 19-21)
      - Transportation-Airports, Chandler. 1987-1994 (Box 426, Folder 1-4)
      - Transportation-Airports, Flagstaff. 1977-1990 (Box 426, Folder 5)
      - Transportation-Airports, Phoenix. 1978 (Box 426, Folder 6)
      - Transportation-Airports, Regional (Arizona). 1993-1994 (Box 426, Folder 7)
      - Transportation-Airports, Sierra Vista. 1992 (Box 426, Folder 8)
      - Transportation-Airports, Tucson International. 1988-1994 (Box 426, Folder 9)
      - Transportation-Airports, Bisbee Douglas International. 1987 (Box 426, Folder 10)
      - Transportation-Airports, Bullhead-Laughlin. 1987-1994 (Box 426, Folder 11)
      - Transportation-Graham County-Safford Bridge. 1992-1993 (Box 426, Folder 12)
      - Transportation-Greyhound Bus. 1990 (Box 426, Folder 13)
      - Transportation-Highway Projects. 1978-1993 (Box 426, Folder 14)
      - Transportation-Williams Grand Canyon Railroad. 1981 (Box 426, Folder 15)
      - Veterans-Projects. 1978-1993 (Box 426, Folder 16)
      - Veterans-State Veterans Cemetery. 1987 (Box 426, Folder 17)
      - Veterans-State Veterans Home. 1987-1990 (Box 426, Folder 18)
      - Veterans-Unified Arizona Veterans. 1989-1993 (Box 426, Folder 19)
      - Veterans-Veterans Administration Medical Centers. 1987-1994 (Box 426, Folder 20)
    - Subseries 2: Media Issues, 1976-1994
      - Abortion. 1985-1994 (Box 426, Folder 21)
      - Agriculture. 1977-1994 (Box 426, Folder 22)
      - Armed Forces-Armstrong Lab. 1992 (Box 426, Folder 23)
      - Armed Forces-Base Closures. 1989-1994 (Box 426, Folder 24)
      - Armed Forces-Ex-Partners of Servicemen for Equality. 1981-1982 (Box 426, Folder 25)
      - Armed Forces-Gays in the Military. 1992-1993 (Box 427, Folder 1)
      - Armed Forces-Military Spending. 1981-1993 (Box 427, Folder 2)
      - Armed Forces-Military Suicides. 1994 (Box 427, Folder 3)
      - Armed Forces-National Guard. 1981-1994 (Box 427, Folder 4)
      - Armed Forces-Perks Bill. 1992-1993 (Box 427, Folder 5)
      - Armed Forces-Sexual Misconduct. 1992-1993 (Box 427, Folder 6)
      - Arms Control-General. 1979-1990 (Box 427, Folder 7)
      - Arms Control-MX Missiles. 1979-1985 (Box 427, Folder 8)
      - Arms Control-SALT II. 1977-1986 (Box 427, Folder 9)
      - Arms Control-Stinger Missiles. 1986-1987 (Box 427, Folder 10)
      - Arms Control-Test Ban Treaty. 1986-1988 (Box 427, Folder 11)
      - Arms Control-Titan II Missiles. 1980-1982 (Box 427, Folder 12)
      - Arts. 1987-1990 (Box 427, Folder 13)
      - Budget-Appropriations. 1978-1990 (Box 427, Folder 14-16)
      - Budget-Balanced Budget. 1979-1990 (Box 427, Folder 17-19)
      - Budget-Bankruptcy Fraud. 1982-1990 (Box 427, Folder 20)
      - Budget-General. 1986-1994 (Box 427, Folder 21-22)
      - Budget-General. 1986-1994 (Box 428, Folder 1)
      - Business. 1977-1993 (Box 428, Folder 2)
      - Children. 1977-1994 (Box 428, Folder 3)
      - Children-Abuse. 1987-1991 (Box 428, Folder 4)
      - Children-Child Care. 1982-1992 (Box 428, Folder 5-6)
      - Children-Head Start. 1993 (Box 428, Folder 7)
      - Children-Health. 1993-1994 (Box 428, Folder 8)
      - Children-Parent Action. 1988-1993 (Box 428, Folder 9)
      - Children-Poverty. 1992 (Box 428, Folder 10)
      - Children-Welfare. 1991-1992 (Box 428, Folder 11)
      - Children-WIC. 1991-1992 (Box 428, Folder 12)
      - Crime-Organized Crime. 1963-1980 (Box 428, Folder 13)
      - Crime-Legislation. 1993-1994 (Box 428, Folder 14-15)
      - Crime-Child Pornography. 1977-1989 (Box 428, Folder 16)
      - Crime-Telemarketing Fraud. 1993 (Box 428, Folder 17)
      - Crime-Violence Against Women Act. 1993 (Box 428, Folder 18)
      - Defense. 1980-1993 (Box 428, Folder 19)
      - Defense-Apache Helicopter. 1981-1993 (Box 428, Folder 20)
      - Defense-Coalition for Peace Through Strength. 1978-1984 (Box 428, Folder 21)
      - Defense-Hughes Missile Systems Group. 1983-1988 (Box 428, Folder 22)
      - Defense-Nominations; Halpern, Morton. 1993 (Box 428, Folder 23)
      - Defense-Nominations; Tower, John. 1989 (Box 429, Folder 1)
      - Defense-Satellite Imagery. 1994 (Box 429, Folder 2)
      - Democratic Party. 1984-1987 (Box 429, Folder 3)
      - Democratic Party-1984 Platform. 1984 (Box 429, Folder 4)
      - Democratic Party-Democratic Policy Commission. 1985-1986 (Box 429, Folder 5-7)
      - Drugs-Committee on Narcotics Abuse and Control. 1979-1981 (Box 429, Folder 8)
      - Drugs-Department of Defense. 1985-1989 (Box 429, Folder 9)
      - Drugs-Drug Air Interdiction. 1979-1985 (Box 429, Folder 10)
      - Drugs-Drug Control Efforts. 1979-1980 (Box 429, Folder 11)
      - Drugs-Education/Intelligence. 1983-1993 (Box 429, Folder 12)
      - Drugs-Funding-Legislature. 1985-1987 (Box 429, Folder 13-14)
      - Drugs-Funding Reports. 1983-1990 (Box 429, Folder 15-16)
      - Drugs-General. 1984-1993 (Box 429, Folder 17)
      - Drugs-General. 1984-1993 (Box 430, Folder 1-2)
      - Drugs-Intelligence. 1988-1993 (Box 430, Folder 3)
      - Drugs-Legislation/Enforcement. 1979-1993 (Box 430, Folder 4)
      - Drugs-Nominations; Dupnik, Clarence. 1992 (Box 430, Folder 5)
      - Drugs-Strategy. 1991-1994 (Box 430, Folder 6)
      - Drugs-Use and Crime. 1977-1985 (Box 430, Folder 7-8)
      - Economy-Economic Stimulus Package. 1993 (Box 430, Folder 9)
      - Economy-General. 1987-1994 (Box 430, Folder 10)
      - Economy-Reaganonimcs. 1980-1988 (Box 430, Folder 11-12)
      - Education-General. 1990-1994 (Box 430, Folder 13)
      - Education-Literacy. 1985-1990 (Box 430, Folder 14)
      - Education-School Prayer. 1984 (Box 430, Folder 15)
      - Education-School-to-Work Programs. 1993-1994 (Box 430, Folder 16)
      - Elderly-Abuse. 1990-1993 (Box 431, Folder 1)
      - Elderly-Aging. 1976-1990 (Box 431, Folder 2-3)
      - Elderly-Medicare. 1981-1984 (Box 431, Folder 4)
      - Elderly-Schlomowitz, Fanny. 1993-1994 (Box 431, Folder 5)
      - Elderly-Westward Ho. 1979-1994 (Box 431, Folder 6)
      - Energy-General. 1977-1990 (Box 431, Folder 7-8)
      - Environment-Arizona Wilderness Act. 1982-1990 (Box 431, Folder 9)
      - Environment-Bureau of Reclamation. 1979-1982 (Box 431, Folder 10)
      - Environment-California Desert Protection Act. 1994 (Box 431, Folder 11)
      - Environment-Clean Air. 1989-1990 (Box 431, Folder 12)
      - Environment-Fires. 1994 (Box 431, Folder 13)
      - Environment-Flood Control. 1979-1994 (Box 431, Folder 14)
      - Environment-General. 1979-1994 (Box 431, Folder 15)
      - Environment-Interior Appropriations. 1993-1994 (Box 431, Folder 16)
      - Environment-Land. 1979-1993 (Box 431, Folder 17)
      - Environment-Mining. 1993-1994 (Box 431, Folder 18)
      - Environment-National Water Alliance. 1983-1988 (Box 431, Folder 19)
      - Environment-Nominations; Babbitt, Bruce. 1992-1993 (Box 431, Folder 20)
      - Environment-Oil Spill Liability. 1979-1989 (Box 431, Folder 21)
      - Environment-Recreation Initiative. 1989-1990 (Box 431, Folder 22)
      - Environment-Solid Waste. 1979-1991 (Box 431, Folder 23)
      - Environment-Water. 1982-1994 (Box 431, Folder 24)
      - Environment-Western Coalition. 1978-1984 (Box 431, Folder 25)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council Contributors. 1984-1988 (Box 431, Folder 26)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council Correspondence. 1984-1988 (Box 432, Folder 1)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council Delegate Selection. 1988 (Box 432, Folder 2)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council Dinner. 1986 (Box 432, Folder 3)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council Formation. 1984 (Box 432, Folder 4)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council General. 1973-1988 (Box 432, Folder 5-9)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council Hearings, Chicago. 1984 (Box 432, Folder 10)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council Hearings, Cleveland. 1984 (Box 432, Folder 11)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council Hearings, Detroit. 1984 (Box 432, Folder 12)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council Hearings, Philadelphia. 1984 (Box 432, Folder 13)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council Hearings Press Lists. no date (Box 432, Folder 14)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council Reception. 1988 (Box 432, Folder 15)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council Speeches and Press Releases. 1984-1988 (Box 432, Folder 16-17)
      - Ethnic American Democratic Council Testimonies. 1984 (Box 432, Folder 18)
      - Ethnic Groups-Hispanic Americans. 1977-1990 (Box 432, Folder 19)
      - Ethnic Groups-Italian Americans. 1984-1985 (Box 432, Folder 20)
      - Ethnic Groups-Native Americans, General. 1978-1994 (Box 433, Folder 1-5)
      - Ethnic Groups-Native Americans, Navajo-Hopi Land Dispute. 1985-1994 (Box 433, Folder 6)
      - Finance-Debt. 1985-1994 (Box 433, Folder 7-8)
      - Firearms-Assault Weapons. 1990-1994 (Box 433, Folder 9)
      - Firearms-Brady Bill. 1993-1994 (Box 433, Folder 10)
      - Firearms-Gun Control. 1978-1994 (Box 433, Folder 11-12)
      - Government-Accomplishment in 103rd Congress. 1993-1994 (Box 433, Folder 13)
      - Government-Campaign Finance Reform. 1985-1994 (Box 433, Folder 14-15)
      - Government-Census. 1990-1993 (Box 433, Folder 16)
      - Government-Civil Rights Bill. 1990 (Box 433, Folder 17)
      - Government-Common Cause. 1988-1990 (Box 433, Folder 18)
      - Government-Congressional Pay Raises. 1977-1991 (Box 433, Folder 19)
      - Government-Election Reform. 1982-1989 (Box 433, Folder 20)
      - Government-Equal Access to Justice Act. 1979-1980 (Box 434, Folder 1)
      - Government-Freedom of Information Act. 1981-1985 (Box 434, Folder 2)
      - Government-General. 1977-1994 (Box 434, Folder 3-4)
      - Government-Honorariums. 1977-1989 (Box 434, Folder 5)
      - Government-Legislative Veto. 1983 (Box 434, Folder 6)
      - Government-Line Item Veto. 1986-1989 (Box 434, Folder 7)
      - Government-National and Community Service Act. 1993 (Box 434, Folder 8)
      - Government-NFL/MLK Holiday Conflict. 1990-1993 (Box 434, Folder 9)
      - Government-Presidency. 1980-1981 (Box 434, Folder 10)
      - Government-Reinventing Government. 1993 (Box 434, Folder 11)
      - Government-Responsible Government Bill. 1993 (Box 434, Folder 12)
      - Government-State of the Union Address. 1994 (Box 434, Folder 13)
      - Government-Term Limits. 1977-1994 (Box 434, Folder 14)
      - Government-Voting. 1981-1993 (Box 434, Folder 15)
      - Government-Waste Fraud and Abuse Amendment. 1975-1986 (Box 434, Folder 16-17)
      - Health-Begay, Lorraine. 1988-1990 (Box 434, Folder 18)
      - Health-Dietary Supplements. 1993 (Box 434, Folder 19)
      - Health-Elders, Jocelyn. 1993 (Box 434, Folder 20)
      - Health-Hanta Virus. 1993 (Box 434, Folder 21)
      - Health-Healthcare. 1979-1994 (Box 434, Folder 22-24)
      - Health-Healthcare Reform. 1993-1994 (Box 434, Folder 25-26)
      - Health-Healthcare Reform. 1993-1994 (Box 435, Folder 1-3)
      - Housing-General. 1990-1994 (Box 435, Folder 4)
      - Human Rights-Helsinki Commission. 1988-1994 (Box 435, Folder 5-7)
      - Human Rights-Office of Special Investigations. 1979-1985 (Box 435, Folder 8)
      - Human Rights-Refuseniks. 1981-1988 (Box 435, Folder 9)
      - Immigration-General. 1988-1994 (Box 435, Folder 10)
      - Immigration-Legislature. 1977-1990 (Box 435, Folder 11-12)
      - Intelligence-Ames, Aldrich. 1994 (Box 435, Folder 13-14)
      - Intelligence-Banca Nazionale del Lavoro. 1993 (Box 435, Folder 15)
      - Intelligence-Counterintelligence Bill. 1994 (Box 435, Folder 16)
      - Intelligence-General. 1993-1994 (Box 436, Folder 1-2)
      - Intelligence-National Reconnaissance Office. 1994 (Box 436, Folder 3-4)
      - Intelligence-Security Classification Act. 1994 (Box 436, Folder 5)
      - Intelligence-Terrorism. 1985-1994 (Box 436, Folder 6)
      - International Relations-Angola. 1986-1994 (Box 436, Folder 7-8)
      - International Relations-Central America. 1980-1988 (Box 436, Folder 9)
      - International Relations-China. 1978-1994 (Box 436, Folder 10)
      - International Relations-Chernobyl. 1989-1992 (Box 436, Folder 11)
      - International Relations-Cuba. 1982-1988 (Box 436, Folder 12)
      - International Relations-El Salvador. 1980-1993 (Box 436, Folder 13)
      - International Relations-Ethiopia. 1985 (Box 436, Folder 14)
      - International Relations-Foreign Aid. 1991-1993 (Box 436, Folder 15-16)
      - International Relations-General. 1977-1994 (Box 436, Folder 17)
      - International Relations-Haiti. 1987-1994 (Box 436, Folder 18)
      - International Relations-Iran. 1980-1987 (Box 436, Folder 19)
      - International Relations-Israel. 1977-1993 (Box 437, Folder 1-2)
      - International Relations-Italy. 1977-1980 (Box 437, Folder 3)
      - International Relations-Kuwait. 1991 (Box 437, Folder 4)
      - International Relations-Lebanon. 1983-1985 (Box 437, Folder 5)
      - International Relations-Mexico. 1979-1989 (Box 437, Folder 6-7)
      - International Relations-Microenterprise Development. 1987-1994 (Box 437, Folder 8)
      - International Relations-Panama. 1978-1989 (Box 437, Folder 9)
      - International Relations-Persian Gulf. 1987-1988 (Box 437, Folder 10)
      - International Relations-Philippines. 1985-1986 (Box 437, Folder 11)
      - International Relations-Shelter Afrique. 1990-1993 (Box 437, Folder 12)
      - International Relations-Somalia. 1993 (Box 437, Folder 13)
      - International Relations-South Africa. 1985-1988 (Box 437, Folder 14)
      - International Relations-South Korea. 1983-1994 (Box 437, Folder 15)
      - International Relations-Soviet Union. 1977-1991 (Box 437, Folder 16)
      - International Relations-Tibet. 1991-1993 (Box 437, Folder 17)
      - Judiciary-Casey, William. 1981-1993 (Box 437, Folder 18)
      - Judiciary-Legislative, Appropriations. 1993 (Box 437, Folder 19)
      - Judiciary-Legislative-Equal Access to Justice Act. 1983 (Box 437, Folder 20)
      - Judiciary-Legislative, Federal Courts Improvement Bill. 1979-1981 (Box 437, Folder 21)
      - Judiciary-Legislative, Judicial Conduct and Reform. 1977-1982 (Box 437, Folder 22)
      - Judiciary-Legislative, Magistrate Act. 1977-1979 (Box 437, Folder 23)
      - Judiciary-Legislative, Special Deputation. 1984-1993 (Box 438, Folder 1)
      - Judiciary-Legislative, Sports Gambling. 1990 (Box 438, Folder 2)
      - Judiciary-Legislative, Sunshine Act. 1979 (Box 438, Folder 3)
      - Judiciary-Legislative; Meese, Edwin. 1988 (Box 438, Folder 4)
      - Judiciary-Legislative; Napolitano, Janet. 1993 (Box 438, Folder 5)
      - Judiciary-Nominations. 1980-1994 (Box 438, Folder 6-8)
      - Judiciary-Reno, Janet. 1993-1994 (Box 438, Folder 9)
      - Judiciary-Vesco, Robert L. 1980 (Box 438, Folder 10)
      - Labor-General. 1978-1994 (Box 438, Folder 11)
      - Law Enforcement-Border Control. 1987-1994 (Box 438, Folder 12)
      - Law Enforcement-Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms. 1982-1993 (Box 438, Folder 13)
      - Law Enforcement-Gang Resistance Education and Training. 1992-1993 (Box 438, Folder 14)
      - Law Enforcement-General. 1983-1994 (Box 438, Folder 15)
      - Legal System-Bilingual, Hearing and Speech Impaired Court Interpreter Act. 1977 (Box 438, Folder 16)
      - Legal System-Board of Legal Services. 1982 (Box 438, Folder 17)
      - Legal System-Bureau of Prisons. 1993 (Box 438, Folder 18)
      - Legal System-Death Penalty. 1977-1987 (Box 438, Folder 19)
      - Legal System-Hanigan Brothers Trial. 1979-1980 (Box 438, Folder 20)
      - Legal System-McBride Principles and U.S. Companies in Northern Ireland Report. 1989 (Box 438, Folder 21)
      - Legal System-Public Integrity. 1979-1981 (Box 438, Folder 22)
      - Patents-General. 1977-1994 (Box 438, Folder 23)
      - Press and Politics. 1979-1994 (Box 438, Folder 24-25)
      - Social Security. 1980-1994 (Box 438, Folder 26)
      - Social Security. 1980-1994 (Box 439, Folder 1)
      - Social Services-Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). 1989 (Box 439, Folder 2)
      - Social Services-Family. 1986-1993 (Box 439, Folder 3)
      - Social Services-Food Stamps. 1992-1993 (Box 439, Folder 4)
      - Social Services-Welfare Reform. 1994 (Box 439, Folder 5)
      - Taxation-Employee Stock Option Ownership. 1977-1981 (Box 439, Folder 6)
      - Taxation-Flat Tax. 1976-1986 (Box 439, Folder 7-10)
      - Taxation-Flat Tax, The Flat Tax (Book). 1985 (Box 439, Folder 11)
      - Taxation-Flat Tax, Low Tax, Simple Tax (Book). 1983 (Box 439, Folder 12)
      - Taxation-Football Games. 1990-1992 (Box 439, Folder 13)
      - Taxation-General. 1977-1991 (Box 439, Folder 14)
      - Taxation-Reaganomics. 1980-1988 (Box 439, Folder 15-16)
      - Technology-General. 1987-1990 (Box 439, Folder 17)
      - Telecommunications-Cable Regulation. 1980-1993 (Box 439, Folder 18)
      - Telecommunications-General. 1993 (Box 439, Folder 19)